<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<docParts>
    <part id="CompareToReturns">
        <returns>
            An integer that indicates whether this instance precedes, follows, or is equal to
            the other in the sort order.
            <list type="table">
                <listheader>
                    <term>Value</term>
                    <description>Condition</description>
                </listheader>
                <item>
                    <term>Less than zero</term>
                    <description>This instance precedes the other in the sort order.</description>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <term>Zero</term>
                    <description>This instance is equal to the other.</description>
                </item>
                <item>
                    <term>Greater than zero</term>
                    <description>
                        This instance follows the other in the sort order
                        or the other is <see langword="null" />.
                    </description>
                </item>
            </list>
        </returns>
    </part>
    <part id="MetadataIdentifiers">
        <remarks>
            <para>The build metadata is a series of dot separated identifiers separated from the
            rest of the version number with a plus sign ('<c>+</c>'). Valid metadata identifiers are
            non-empty and consist of ASCII alphanumeric characters and hyphens (<c>[0-9A-Za-z-]</c>).</para>

            <para>The metadata does not affect precedence. Two version numbers differing only in
            build metadata have the same precedence. However, metadata does affect sort order. An
            otherwise identical version without metadata sorts before one that has metadata.</para>
        </remarks>
    </part>
    <part id="PrereleaseIdentifiers">
        <remarks>
            <para>A prerelease version is denoted by appending a hyphen ('<c>-</c>') and a series
            of dot separated identifiers immediately following the patch version number. Each
            prerelease identifier may be numeric or alphanumeric. Valid numeric identifiers consist
            of ASCII digits (<c>[0-9]</c>) without leading zeros. Valid alphanumeric identifiers are
            non-empty strings of ASCII alphanumeric and hyphen characters (<c>[0-9A-Za-z-]</c>) with
            at least one non-digit character.</para>

            <para>Prerelease versions have lower precedence than release versions. Prerelease
            version precedence is determined by comparing each prerelease identifier in order from
            left to right. Numeric identifiers have lower precedence than alphanumeric identifiers.
            Numeric identifiers are compared numerically. Alphanumeric identifiers are compared
            lexically in ASCII sort order.</para>
        </remarks>
    </part>
    <part id="PrecedenceOrder">
        <remarks>
            <para>Precedence order is determined by comparing the major, minor, patch, and prerelease
            portion in order from left to right. Versions that differ only by build metadata have the
            same precedence. The major, minor, and patch version numbers are compared numerically. A
            prerelease version precedes a release version.</para>

            <para>The prerelease portion is compared by comparing each prerelease identifier from
            left to right. Numeric prerelease identifiers precede alphanumeric identifiers. Numeric
            identifiers are compared numerically. Alphanumeric identifiers are compared lexically
            in ASCII sort order. A longer series of prerelease identifiers follows a shorter series
            if all the preceding identifiers are equal.</para>
        </remarks>
    </part>
    <part id="SortOrder">
        <remarks>
            <para>Sort order is consistent with precedence order, but provides an order for versions
            with the same precedence. Sort order is determined by comparing the major, minor,
            patch, prerelease portion, and build metadata in order from left to right. The major,
            minor, and patch version numbers are compared numerically. A prerelease version precedes
            a release version.</para>
            <para>The prerelease portion is compared by comparing each prerelease identifier from
            left to right. Numeric prerelease identifiers precede alphanumeric identifiers. Numeric
            identifiers are compared numerically. Alphanumeric identifiers are compared lexically
            in ASCII sort order. A longer series of prerelease identifiers follows a shorter series
            if all the preceding identifiers are equal.</para>
            <para>Otherwise equal versions without build metadata precede those with metadata. The
            build metadata is compared by comparing each metadata identifier. Identifiers are
            compared lexically in ASCII sort order. A longer series of metadata identifiers follows
            a shorter series if all the preceding identifiers are equal.</para>
        </remarks>
    </part>
</docParts>